feedbackexpress.com 2019-09-29

# Privacy Policy - FeedbackExpress

FeedbackExpress remain fully committed to the protection of your privacy at all times. The information contained in this privacy policy has been published to inform you of the way in which any Personal Data you provide us with or we collect from you will be used. Please read this information carefully in order to fully understand how we treat such Personal Data.

When you access or use FeedbackExpress, you agree to our privacy policy and you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your Personal Data for the purpose of making FeedbackExpress and/or the Service available to you, in accordance with this policy.

We will collect, store, use and disclose Personal Data in accordance with all applicable laws relating to the protection of Personal Data, including the EU Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC, the EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679, the EU ePrivacy Directive 2002/58/EC as amended by Directive 2009/136/EC, as amended or superseded from time to time, and any national implementing legislation (“Data Protection Laws”).

For the purpose of Data Protection Laws, in relation to any Personal Data you submit to our service, you will be the “Data Controller” and we will be a “Data processor” of such Personal Data, as defined by the GDPR [here](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/key-definitions/).

 **1\. Personal Data We May Collect from You**

“Personal Data” as defined by the GDPR [here](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/key-definitions/).

Personal Data can be collected and processed when our website is in operation by you. We may obtain and use the following Personal Data:

  * Any correspondence we have with you should you contact us. Data you provide when you fill out forms on our Website, including but not limited to data you provide when you register to become a user of the Service.
  * Details of transactions made by you through the Website.
  * Details of your visits to our Website, which includes without limitation location and traffic data, weblogs, resources you access and other communication data.

You represent and warrant that you i) have the right to transfer such Personal Data to us for the purpose of receiving the Service; and ii) are solely responsible for obtaining all required consents, authorisations and permissions from such Users and third parties and providing all required notifications to such Users and third parties (where applicable) to enable you to provide such information to us and to grant to us the rights set forth in this privacy policy. You may not provide us with any Client Data or other information containing Personal Data of Users or third parties unless and until you have obtained all necessary consents, authorisations and permissions to do so.

 **2.  Use of Cookies**

Circumstances may arise when we may need to gather information about your computer to help provide appropriate services or products to you.  The data gathered is solely statistical data, which may be shared with advertisers.

The facts collected about you are statistical only. No identifying information will be shared about our visitors and how they made use of our site.  No personal details will ever be shared.

Cookies are used to collect general online usage by using a cookie file.  If used this cookie file is downloaded without prompting.  It will be placed on your hard drive with information transferred to the hard drive allowing the cookies to be used for data collection.  A cookie is used to improve any services/ products, or overall website characteristic we offer you.

Any computer has the option to decline cookies.  Your web browser options include an “enable” button to decline cookies.  It is imperative that you understand by declining cookies you may be limiting your access to sections of our website.

If our advertisers use cookies it will result from a click on their advertisement, and we do not have control over their cookies if used.

2.1 Google Analytics **  
**

We use Google Analytics to collect information about how visitors use the Site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. For more information about Google’s privacy policy, please visit: [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/)

If you do not wish to allow the use of Google Analytics cookies at all, Google provides an opt-out plug-in for most common website browsers: [Opt out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

2.2 Google Adwords

We use Google Adwords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the FeedbackExpress website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.

2.3 Facebook

We use Facebook cookies to understand the effectiveness of our Facebook advertising campaigns and to compare the performance of those campaigns to ads displayed on other websites and apps. For more information about Facebook’s privacy policy, please visit: [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/)

 **3\. Storing Your Data**

3.1 Secured servers are used by our company to ensure proper data storage. Information on transactions is kept encrypted for safety measures.

3.2 We take all necessary steps to provide the best security available. Where needed a password may be necessary to access areas of our site. You are responsible for the safety and confidentiality of the password you generate.

 **4\. Protecting Your Data**

We will take reasonable steps to maintain appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect the Data you provide to us against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure of, or access to your Data.

 **5\. Use of **  Data**  
**

Information stored and collected about you allows us to improve our services or products for you. Added to this parameter, we may use your information for the following purposes:

5.1 Any commitment we make on a contracted basis.

5.2 Notification re- changes or improvements may be sent to you in regards to product or service changes that could affect our service to you.

5.3 Existing customers can be contacted on the topic of goods or services related to a previous sale, if we feel you might be interested in these additional topics.

5.4 Identifiable data, which could be used to disclose who you are, is never shared.

 **6\. Third Party Integration Partners**

We will never supply your Data to third parties unless under the conditions stated beneath this section of our privacy policy. We may aggregate and anonymise your data and share such aggregated and anonymised Data with third parties for the purpose of data analytics and providing the service, and/or in order to fulfil the obligations we have in relation to any contracts we have in place with you.

 **7\. Your Rights**

We may at times provide links on our Website to third party websites, including without limitation those owned or managed by our partner networks, affiliates or advertisers. These websites have separate privacy policies, and we therefore cannot accept any responsibility for the content. As such, choosing to follow these links is a choice you make at your own risk, and we advise that you check these websites’ individual privacy policies before submitting any personal data.

You retain at all times the right to access/amend/delete and Data we hold about you or to exercise your right of data portability or to object to, or restrict, the purposes for which your Data is processed on certain grounds. You may exercise this right by making a request in accordance with Data Protection Laws, by emailing legal@feedbackexpress.com. You may also lodge a complaint with the UK data protection regulator, the Information Commissioner should you be dissatisfied with the way that we handle your Data.

You undertake to notify your Users of this privacy policy and of their rights under the Data Protection Law. We will provide you with reasonable assistance to enable you to comply and respond to a request, query or complaint from a User in relation to their Data.

 **8\. How Long We Keep Your Data**

We will keep your Data for the duration of the Service and we may keep your and your Data for a further 21 days past the end of the service to ensure a seamless return if you should decide to restart the service, in accordance with your instructions or for such periods as may be required by law.

 **9\. Changes to the Our Privacy Policy**

If at any time we make a change to this policy, we will update this page to reflect such change. Where we feel it appropriate, we will notify you by email, however, we recommend you review this page periodically to ensure you remain happy with the latest version.

 **10\. Contacting Us**

We welcome and hope you do not hesitate to make any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please contact us at legal@feedbackexpress.com. Please note that calls to or from our business may be monitored or recorded.
